That their team is going to give you a very clear idea, let me start
with ICICI Lombard General Insurance,
something good will happen with this, prevention had to be done, good
numbers, its grandfather is good, strong staff
numbers are coming from the loot side,
I am net premium and add year on year 10 percent, you want to see a
jump of four and a half percent in
profit because healthy growth
in premium income is showing very good growth
year on year, eighty percent, European
around eleven and a half percent,
all the sectors will give you less forward,
I think girls, this is a
good company on the bridge of people, good performance, we
find many options in the past,
large generations, animal options,
hence it remains on the website, keep it in
green today, on the basis of its numbers, a
good company with good packaging
and the second company is Parag Milk Foods,
involved in crime, tomorrow vote Mithun's body
fundraising, play fundraising update,
stock of the year 420 or stock
12000000,
sure, we are going to select this  Its
current affairs 94 and
9490 have been
subscribed,
110 crore 50 lakh
subscribers, on
the other hand,
from the side of the member group, this 20 lakh is
of the south direction,
this is
of the 93.75 dynasty, so it is also using that
on these labels, so this is good news, on this channel, the
message is going on the Twitter account, the
promoters are getting Fateh infection, due to which
hair is falling, keep it green for today, keep it
green for the trade union, your
investment advisor will tell you better,
but the good news is that from the after stock,
it has been kept on the branch, Vedanta is there, the
global mood is good, so the quantity
was in focus like that, that the
news of crude oil is different, along with this there is
also a good news, this Bodh Bhikshu, that if it does
its quality basket, then
everything can be done about it,
secondly, Hindustan Zinc, Hindustan Zinc
and Vedanta have 19 presidents,
this is also why
we, should I just tell you this much, tell us the
whole story, the style of
marriage of 16 stocks, all three MCD
commissioners, BPC and HPC and all three
You know such news about oil producer ONGC Oil, let me
repeat it again
that the government had imposed export duty on gas and petrol-diesel,
it has been reduced - the duty
on petrol-diesel has been
reduced, the
excise duty
on Royal Production which was at 20250 has been reduced to
17000 by removing tent house, so in this way the
excise duty on Vent for Games has been
reduced, this had a
very severe impact on these companies at that time and it turned out to be nutritious,
so I think that due to this news, today
you should keep on the radar the direct benefit or direct loss in the oil and gas space
and that is why we are going to discuss these
six shares from now onwards and give two more in this series
but for now keep these six in mind and the news is
very positive, there will be a lot of
sandwiches in it, how much it fell, how much it rose,
all that is a matter of discussion but right now